Okay, so let's practice using SNS.
So I'm going to go into
the simple notification service console,
and I'm going to create a topic called demo SNS.
Now this topic will leave it
as default for all the options,
and we'll just click simply on create topics.
So the idea is that we want to send messages
to this SNS topic,
and we want subscribers to this topic
to receive the messages.
So we can define subscriptions here currently we have zero,
but it will create a subscription,
and as you can see
we have different protocols for your subscription.
It could be HTTP, HTTPS, Email, Email-JSON, SQS and Lambda.
So lots of different targets for your SNS,
and as you remember, if you send a message to one SNS topic,
then all the subscribers whatever they might,
may be in terms of protocol will receive that message.
For this hands on
we'll just go with email because it's easy.
And for the endpoints,
I'm going to go for stephaneccpdemo@mailinator.com.
Now if you don't know this,
this is a service to get a temporary email address.
So if I click and enter,
if I enter this defense CCP demo mailbox,
this is a temporary mailbox for me.
So I'm going to use this mailbox,
and I'm going to create a subscription.
And now if we go back to the demo SNS topic,
we can see that the subscription is pending confirmation.
Very easy for this to fix it,
I'm gonna go into my Mailinator mailbox and as you can see,
I have an email from AWS,
asking me to confirm my subscription
which I will do right now.
So my subscription ID is confirmed,
and what you could do,
if you are savvy would be to create other subscriptions.
They're more complicated to create besides email,
so we'll just keep it as one for now.
But you could have many subscribers for your SNS topic.
So now what I'm going to do is
to practice sending a message to my SNS topic.
For this I'm going to publish message,
say demo subject line,
and then I will say hello world in terms of payload.
And then finally I'm going to publish this message,
and the message has not been published successfully.
And so all the subscribers in my subscription
should receive that message.
So if we go into Mailinator, go back to my inbox,
I can see that moments ago I received a new email
called demo subject line,
and the content says hello world, so this has worked.
So this is a very simple demo of how SNS works.
And when you're done, you can go ahead and delete the topic.
If you want it too, it won't cost you any money.
So that's it I hope that was helpful,
and I will see you in the next lecture.